Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
And now, for the final match of the selection exam, Rill, Mills, and Ruben of Team I, come forth!
Here, Master Rill, please enjoy a nice cup of herbal tea to clear your mind and boost your creative focus.
Yay! Thanks so much!
When your mother hears of your accomplishments, I'm certain she'll be overjoyed and beaming with pride.
Yeah? She'll be proud? You think so?
Indeed, Master.
Then I've definitely gotta win this.
You are the illustrious captain of the Aqua Deer. Show no mercy in proving that to the enemy.
It's the final match and he's still cool as a cucumber. I guess that's typical for Captain Rill, though.
He has been winning by landslide this entire time.
He's been carrying our team ever since the tournament began.
We might get picked to be Royal Knights just because of his amazing performance.
Where did those two come from?
We need to stand out more!
Team P, N, Yuno, and Noelle, step forward!
For what it's worth, I hope you'll go easy on us.
Brace yourselves for pain! Because our team's going to grind your bones and assault us!
Excuse me, but you know we can hear all that, right?
I'm sorry, it's hard to control my inner monologue.
Give it your all, Noelle!
What's wrong? Your face is as stiff as a rock bed truffle!
Get fired up, kid! Mushrooms are much tastier when they're roasted!
They're good frozen as well!
Anyway, keep your eyes on the prize!
Mush, Noelle! Mush!
Shut up!
Honestly, worrying about Asta's distracting enough already.
I mean, I'm concerned about his health because he's my squadmate!
It doesn't bother me that Mimosa's with him or anything!
Your face is burning up! You're finally on fire to win!
No one asked you!
Those people are so noisy!
If they mess things up, I'll make sure they pay for it!
Belle, let's pull out all the stops.
All right! Now I get a chance to shine!
What'd he say? Does that mean he's been holding back until now?
So cool. I wish I could be like that too.
This is gonna be fun!
Maybe against you, I'll be able to create my next masterpiece!
I doubt that, but I look forward to seeing how much my skills have improved.
Young Master Rill will be victorious!
You know Rill!
No, the Young Master!
No!
Master Rill!
Yes!
Here we go.
This is the match that will decide the winner.
Though I myself won't be playing a starring role, I expect a beautiful performance.
I want to reach new heights from now on, so I won't take my eyes off the action for a second!
See you next week!
Nice!
95!
Thank you.
Let's go back!
You're awake!
Took you long enough, pal.
Where am I?
Where's Longris?
Austin, you need to lie down.
Easy for you to say.
It's over, and that's that.
That's right.
And our team lost.
So how's Finral?
He was severely wounded, so he's in the castle infirmary now.
What about Yuno and his teammates?
They kicked butt and won both matches!
The deciding battle's supposed to be starting any minute.
You know.
It's time for the final face-off!
Team I!
I'm so excited!
We'll stand out this time!
Team P!
I'll take care of the captain of the Aqua Deer.
He's all yours.
And begin!
Oh boy!
Here he comes!
Over here!
Don't have to call him over.
Just as we expected.
That Golden Dawn kid is headed straight for the captain.
This is our chance!
Wind magic.
Wind blade shower.
Go picture magic!
Game of the gods!
I don't like the looks of that dude!
I've never faced an opponent like this before.
So that's what the top newbies like.
I understand now.
Whoa!
They're greeting each other with tough spells right out of the gate, huh?
And from the looks of it, neither of them has reached their full power yet.
What?
That's how they say hello?
Not exactly what I'd call the light.
Look!
There's a fight going on over there as well.
Their team's crystal is directly ahead.
Hurry!
Ice magic!
Ice needle!
There's no magic!
Rock ball!
Both at the same time?
Leave the ice attack to me!
You can handle the other half, right, Noel?
Fungus magic!
Towering Mr. Mushroom!
You, I am!
Now bring it on!
Whoa!
What?
Ah!
Water creation magic!
Sea Dragon Slayer!
Their gourd is up!
Whoa!
If they want a shootout, then we'll just have to give them one!
We'll win this!
We'll destroy that crystal!
And stand out!
The battle's split in two, just the way we planned it.
Now we have to protect our crystal to the end.
So, you handle the captain.
Wind magic!
Tornado fail!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
And now, Crescent Moonsickle!
Here you go!
Ready?
Of course I am!
Wing magic!
Swift white bow!
Whoa!
Jonathan!
Oh.
Whoa!
Yeah.
Hey, that's not bad, but I'm better!
Yeah!
Hmph, looks like I might have misjudged you.
Too bad, really. You need a bit more flair.
He sure knows his way around wind magic spells.
He does have a four-leaf clover grimoire, after all. Impressive.
Yes, but he's fighting the captain of the Aqua Deer, who's got quite an artful defense strategy.
Oh, what an adorable spirit. This is getting interesting.
Still though, I don't think you've given me enough inspiration to paint my greatest masterpiece yet, so let's keep going!
What's this jerk's problem? Using his weird art projects to block everything!
Belle, it's time.
I've been saving this to use against Asta during the finals. But he's a magic knight captain.
So he's worthy!
Yuno had once controlled his mana using the heightened focus he developed during a battle in which he was deprived of all five senses.
After that, with his training using mana skin to envelop himself in a protective barrier, the young magic knight was able to master a method of gathering enormous amounts of mana inside his body.
Then, he honed this skill even further, to the point that he finally learned how to harness not only his own mana, but the spirit's power as well.
I'm becoming one with my Yuno! I love it!
Asta, this is where I leave you in the dust. Between us, I'll always be the winner.
Asta, it's there, let's weaponryö!
Spirit, let's tidak-
Spirit assimilation. Spirit dive.
Whoa, look how much power he's generating!
It's beautiful.
Mastering an ability like that requires tremendous strength and finely honed intuition.
Well done, Yuno.
Wow!
Young Master.
That's a really cool trick, Yuno!
Thanks to you, I feel like I could paint anything in the world!
Now win spirit magic!
Picture magic!
Spirit Storm!
Scream of the mystical dragon, please!
It might work. Just look at it.
Blazerou, will you stop this incessant painting?
You're too much for us!
One day, even your mother will come to understand your unique talent.
This is great!
I never thought a fight like this could make me feel so happy!
You look amazing!
So strong!
No!
Why?
Yuno's supposed to be battling me!
I'll win.
Even if he is a captain.
Then...
I'll win!
There! See? You're getting it now!
Ah!
More power!
Keep it coming!
We're gonna paint my most brilliant masterpiece together!
We're gonna put it together!
Ah!
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!
WHAT?! How'd this happen?!
We were just getting to the fun part and everything!
Do we really have to stop fighting now?!
I don't understand! Why did it shatter?!
Well, you see, Rill unleashed a devastating amount of magic power.
I suppose the crystal couldn't withstand it all.
Wasn't that their crystal?
How foolish.
We didn't...
Captain Rill has destroyed his own team's crystal!
Which means, the victory belongs to Yuno, Noelle, and Anne of Team P!
Talk about an unexpected ending.
That final clash of magic power gave me goosebumps!
It looks like that rookie's ability is on par with Captain Rill's.
In fact, I wouldn't be surprised if it's even greater than that.
All right!
They did win, but only because the other team sabotaged themselves.
There's no sense getting a big head over it.
I can't take another loss after this one.
So it's back to training for me.
It's over! This isn't any fun at all!
Young Master, please dry your tears.
In my entirely biased and arbitrary opinion, you were the one true victor in this battle.
Huh? You mean it? I was the winner?
By a landslide.
Uh, yeah, I don't think so, Gramps.
Not a chance.
Indeed, the young Master may not have won anything in practical terms.
But still, failure can be a springboard.
Let it propel you toward a new masterpiece.
I am certain that is what Madam would want for you.
I think so, too.
Thanks for your help, Walt.
And you know?
Thank you.
Ah!
Sweet, sweet victory!
We flexed our muscles!
That was great.
Of course.
What'd you expect?
No!
Oh my gosh!
I can't believe we actually did it!
The Royal Knights' Selection Exam is now over.
Good work, Team P.
My congratulations.
And regardless of the result,
you all should be proud of winning the semifinal.
Oh, and just because the other teams were eliminated along the way,
that doesn't mean anyone's out of the running.
We're going to give each individual contestant's performance a comprehensive review,
and then we'll select 10 to 20 Royal Knights at a later date.
Oh!
Awesome!
That means I've still got a shot!
Everyone here is a remarkably talented Magic Knight.
It won't be an easy decision, that's for sure.
In closing, we have a special message from the King.
Ahem!
You have all done exceedingly well.
Exchanging sophisticated spells,
your uncanny ability to adapt and innovate in a variety of situations,
and, of course, your keen execution of precise battle strategies.
Really, any team here could have been the one to emerge victorious from where I'm sitting.
He sounds like a real king.
So proper.
Maybe too proper.
This doesn't seem right somehow.
However!
I still worked harder than any of you!
If not for me, there would be no tournament!
I was the one who announced that the strongest would be selected to join the Royal Knights!
I am single-handedly responsible for this whole event!
What are you waiting for?!
Shower me with praise!
Thank you, Your Majesty, but please relax.
We're all here because we heartily endorse the appointment of the Royal Knights
and eagerly await the announcement.
Look, think about it this way.
These warriors are devoting themselves to defeating the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
And isn't that far more rewarding than any praise?
The Wizard King is so much better.
If only he was the one ruling us!
Can't we just make him the king from now on?
Now then, whoever makes it into the Royal Knights, I'll be counting on you!
Sir!
Curse you, Julius!
You're always hugging the spotlight!
And with that, the Royal Knights selection exam is now complete!
Well, that's that.
I'd say today's contest was a success.
Indeed.
It fulfilled your other goal, too.
We've potentially discovered the Magic Knight being used as a puppet by the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
As soon as Longris recovers, we'll conduct a full investigation.
I don't want to make everyone a suspect, but there may be more to come.
We can't let our guard down.
Thanks for staying with me, Mimosa.
Yes, of course.
My magic may be able to heal wounds of the body, but wounds of the spirit...
Ready?
We're leaving.
You know!
What?
Now?
I see.
Asta.
You've done enough.
I can look after him now.
Um, I mean, don't take it the wrong way!
Yeah, squad mates are supposed to help each other!
That's all I'm talking about!
You know...
You don't want to say goodbye, at least?
You know!
I will catch up to you!
I will be the Wizard King!
I swear!
I don't feel like being caught up to...
Hey, slow down!
No!
I'm friends!
You made this?
Sure, he may be a little rough around the edges, but the important thing is that he's a man of his word!
A warrior who's secretly protecting his country!
We trust each other like lifelong friends and face death together every day!
Friends.
Trust.
Now, those aren't things I think about too often.
Leaving already?
Yeah.
Thank you for telling those who lost their battles where they went wrong.
While I can't applaud the manner in which you did, I'm certain those who wish to grow will heed your advice and be stronger for it.
We need your trap magic and your ability to think critically.
The exam is done, and you likely passed.
I hope you'll join.
What are you talking about?
I might have kept the rest of them guessing.
But smart money says you've known since this whole thing started that I wasn't Zerk's Lutner.
See ya.
Quite right.
I'm not pleased that you impersonated someone else.
But, since you are a magic knight, you're still qualified.
Zora.
I met a certain purple orca on the battlefield long ago.
His name was Zara Ideale.
He did everything in his power to keep his kingdom safe.
The very model of a magic knight.
I fought alongside a real tough character on the battlefield today.
He definitely knew impressive ways to use time magic.
The guy's on his way to the top, that's for sure.
Nova Crono, I think.
Even his name is cool.
To ensure commoners like him were acknowledged,
I developed a system that awards knights based on their merit instead of their status.
Yet there are still those among the magic knights who could learn from a man like that.
Isn't it time that you wore your robe?
The robe of your true squad, Zora Ideale.
I don't know who you're talking about.
Me?
I'm just some lame excuse for a super mage who happened to be passing through.
Hello there, the lovely Kirsch Vermillion at your service.
What incredible beauty lies ahead as the story continues to unfold?
Black Clover, page 85, together in the bath.
My naked form is too exquisite to gaze upon.
Black Clover, page 79, and Pang?
Black Clover, page 80, and Language 80, and Black Clover, page 81, andена了.
Black Clover, page 91, andена ratedудь, page 71, and masterben, and Ast absolv眾 of Alexander comenze follow the documents.
Brys Absolutely forever!
Again, don't harm to all myRL drove and Woался Ampice brand.
With what banget him got you in his role.
Goodbye, Red appro Бог.
You can see and do it.
By the way, that seems like he wanted usage.
Thanks for the circumcision traz.
But it seems like you're not going on.
The position here, don't listen.
The next step, I think so much has to do it.
What about you eat in here.
The next step is where I can forget,
You can see that that.